Amanda L. Himlan

amandahimlan@yahoo.com 671 Mount Hope Street North Attleboro, MA 02760 (508) 695-6735

Profile:

Highly motivated and energetic administrative professional with over 8 years of experience in office administration and project support. Proven ability to effectively multi-task and manage priorities in a fast-paced environment. Seeking part-time position in an organization that values a hard-working team member.

Experience

Verano Office Administrator

January 2007 – Present July 2004 - March 2006

- Worked closely with Executive Management Team in support of company's initiatives.
- Prepared/Assisted Marketing with quarterly newsletters, web conferences, mailings and internet research.
- Maintained current documentation on Company's website and employee intra-web.
- Tracked and reported monthly Sales commission earnings for CFO.
- Maintained confidential employment, payroll, benefits files and prepared semi-monthly payroll for US and Canada offices.
- Entered Accounts Payable utilizing Great Plains system.
- Provided initial point of contact for callers, visitors and corporate email inquiries.
- Maintained office and office equipment; communicated with landlord and vendors as needed.
- Coordinated meeting and travel logistics.

Accenture - Institute for High Performance Business

March 2000 - July 2004

Executive Assistant/Office Manager

- Executive Assistant Responsibilities:
 - Supported two Associate Partners/Senior Research Fellows.
 - Managed three executive calendars in Microsoft Outlook.
 - Arranged conference calls, videoconferences, domestic and international travel and face to face meetings.
 - Performed internet research and analysis.
- Office Management Responsibilities:
 - Established new contractor accounts which included, preparing written contractor agreements, coordinating laptop rentals, arranging network access, enabling phone accounts and being a direct point of contact for individuals.
 - Prepared/submitted vendor/contractor invoices to Accounts Payable and followed through to ensure payment in a timely manner.
 - Operated and maintained technical video/audio conferencing system, including organizing training for office employees.
 - Arranged meeting and events in Cambridge location.
 - Reported maintenance problems to building management company.
 - Ordered/maintained stock of office supplies.

NEPTCO, Incorporated

Sept 1999 - March 2000

Temporary Office Position

Created and maintained current product line data sheets utilizing Adobe PageMaker.

Boston Children's Hospital

July 1998 – July 1999

Urology Department Administrative Associate II

Scheduled and coordinated physician's daily activities and arranged patient appointments.

Education

University of Massachusetts, Amherst Bachelor of Science, Human Nutrition

May 1998

Computer Skills

Proficient with Microsoft Outlook, Word, Excel, WordPerfect, Adobe PageMaker and Great Plains.

References

Available upon request.